Music
Finalists #12 who attended a training camp to strengthen their assigned songs to be performed at the final judging on April 19.
Like, it's okay because I could sing it without getting the pitch wrong.
It's not like that.
It's really about conveying everyone's feelings through dance and song.
It's really a performance to convey everyone's feelings through dance and song.
As it is now, we are all a bit unprotective of each other.
You know, like when you make a mistake in the lyrics.
or looking down when we should be dancing forward
It was frustrating to not be able to do what I wanted to be conscious of.
Sachina Aokawa, who had never danced or sung before
She said that her lack of confidence in her technical skills led to a passive performance.
At today's concert,
to the children who took part in the concert for the first time.
She also talked about how moved she felt and how she heard the children's voices,
He also talked about how he heard the children's voices.
I was trying so hard not to make mistakes that I couldn't express my emotions at all.
Runa Minami said,
It is still difficult for me to sing and dance,
It is still difficult for me to sing and dance, so it is still difficult for me to sing and dance, so I am not able to sing and dance as I thought I would.
If things continue as they are now, all of them will fail the competition.
This was the reality that the 10 students were confronted with at the camp.
Even the dance instructor said
When I went to the stage
Everyone is dancing.
I think that's the way we dance.
I think it's the way we dance, so
When you teach us how to dance
They're all dancing.
I think that's the way we dance, so this was the reality that the 10 of us were confronted with at the camp.
And the teacher who taught them how to dance
I don't think we are ready to be on stage.
At that time, there were already 17 days until the final judging.
Six days after the camp, the day of the independent training for the finalists
Good morning.
I was pretty much handing the baton to the B-team... and they were handing it off with a proper hand gesture.
I was like, "What the heck?
You handed it to them rather clearly. I'm better.
It's like you're thinking about it.
I guess so. When I was down to just Dorora, the only help I got was...
I'm making her sing in the bamboo.
I'm sure.
Here, with Ruru-chan
You're dancing out your affection too much
Because Ruru-chan is too far behind
Let's go with Modoka-chan. That's right.
I have to be in the front,
Do you do this when you sing?
When I do this, I'll turn my head this way, so I'll be facing this way the whole time.
If I'm in sync with you, I'll put my face like this.
Did you come forward first?
Yes, I did come out like this.
That's fine,
What do you want me to do?
It's possible that my voice will come out,
There's a chance it's going to come out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But why don't you go that way?
But you're in the middle, so you might as well take the easy way out.
But I don't know what to do then.
Do it this way.
Okay.
Do you remember how to hold it when you catch it? Hands, and... and... and... and... and here? Feet, oh, right.
And next, body movement.
Ms. Minami, who had never danced or sung before, did me at the camp.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Takatan, chakachakai, shin, two, ai.
At the beginning, she was far behind in dance formations, etc.
I had a gap between the camp and this period of time, and I would get sick during that time, and also, I had to do my homework for school,
When I arrived at the beginning, I thought my body was a little bit born,
But I have decided to give it my all and run through the audition to the end,
Anyway, I will do my best to do what I can do.
Anyway, I will do everything I can with all my might.
I could sense from her words that she really wanted to become an idol.
Can we do something here? Oh! Great!
That's good!
Regardless of the group, we're all in it together.
We've rented a studio to practice.
We're going to practice hard until the 19th.
We have no choice but to do it.
Actually, the girls have been calling each other after the camp.
They gathered when they could and practiced while pointing out each other's shortcomings.
Sena Hiroshima, who had never sung or danced before, was highly praised by everyone around her. Today is today,
In today, I couldn't do anything
In me just smiling
Ms. Hiroshima, in fact, had a certain problem. In the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today In the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today, in the midst of today,  I want to fix my own singing, and I want to do it by myself.
I wanted to fix it more.
Even in the camp
I always start the song with "Hiroshima-san"...
Hiroshima-san doesn't put it in properly.
I need to make sure I put in the "korode-" part properly,
I couldn't hear "Koronde-den" and "Koro-".
So,
The part about the treasure I received,
If Mr. Hiroshima makes a mistake, Mr. Yamamoto will not be able to put it in,
I think there is a phenomenon that if Mr. Hiroshima makes a mistake, Mr. Yamamoto will not be able to enter the treasure.
A little bit, a little bit, a little bit. It is difficult. If you overflow something high, it becomes a little bit too much.
A little bit, a little bit, a little bit.
Isn't it difficult?
When it comes to important moments, I get nervous
I can't show my strength as I want to.I can't show my strength as much as I want to.
I really can't go on like this.
That's what I've been thinking the most.
Practice and practice again and again
I tried to compensate for my nervousness
I tried to compensate for my nervousness.
And the other members, too,
I thought that I should be able to show them what I could do without a mirror.
I want to be able to dance and sing in a way that is fun to watch.
Only 6 days have passed since the training camp, where they were confronted with a harsh reality.
It was impressive to see their faces as if they had gained a little confidence.
Then came the day of the final judging. Nervous, excited, and no doubt anxious, the finalists were filled with a variety of emotions.
The finalists were surprisingly relaxed.
They were smiling more than ever, eager to enjoy the live performance.
The final judging consisted of two parts: an individual singing performance in front of the PhilAvo members and a group performance in front of the audience.
The time for the performance was gradually approaching.
The pianists find even the smallest amount of time to practice. I want to be a father to these 10 people who are pursuing their dream of becoming idols, and I want to thank my parents for giving me the opportunity to experience so much.
I want to thank them for giving me the opportunity to experience so many things.
I am determined to make it to the end!
I've been through a lot of auditions,
But now that I'm 21 years old, this is where my life is going to part ways.
I knew that if I didn't audition for Beer Jump, I would regret it,
I want to do my best so that I don't have any regrets. I want to give a good performance as an idol.
As they practiced hard, they eventually began to help each other and give each other advice,
A bond was formed.
We've become really close,
I really feel like today is the end. The children who took part in the workshop were very excited to see how well they got along with each other.
The children who participated said, "We've become really close,
I don't know if it really ends today.
I don't want to leave because the 10 of us are so close.
The children who participated felt like just a little bit of kindness went down their throats!
If only that one word overflowed
This baton will continue
forever.
In the midst of all this
They all said, "Open this," so
I'll open it here.
What is this?
It says "kuchen" on the left eye.
Kuchen and cookies and cookies.
Oh, no.
No, it's not.
With sweets in hand to help you relax a little
Building up leader Mr. Matsumura visiting the finalists.
They've all grown so much since I saw them at the camp.
Please perform with confidence and a smile on your face.
I'm sure you will be nervous, but not too nervous,
I think you will be nervous, but if you get too nervous, it will be very difficult,
I hope you can show everything you've done so far,
I hope you'll do your best.
I'm sure you will be nervous, but if you are too nervous, it will be very difficult. Thank you very much.
At first, I didn't like it,
But everyone worked really hard,
They told me they wanted to join Pill Up,
I was very happy to see how hard they were working.
I am determined to do my best to make Pill-up even bigger and better.
Tough at first!
I don't want to be attendance number 1 ever again!
Finally, the final judging begins!
First, individual singing in front of the filler-apologists.
Singing? Wait, I'm scared.
Wait, I'm the first one, so somebody's got to go for it.
Go for it!
Hang in there, cheapskate!
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there, it's gonna be okay!
Go to the stage with a little apprehension.
Yes, we will proceed in the form of a final check for auditions... Music
When I fell and got covered in mud
The hand that helped me when I fell and got muddy
Ever.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Rina Ikuta.
Her voice was really loud earlier as well.
She's growing up so much, and her expression...
I feel like she's less confused than before.
I don't know...
Wow, that's really something.
I've got nine days left.
I don't have 9 more days.
My heart...
I want to repay my parents by becoming an idol.
I was talking with Rena Sakurai, who hopes with a strong desire.
After this, those who attended the event
"I want them to sing loudly.
I want them to sing in a loud voice.
I want them to sing in a loud voice. I want them to sing in a loud voice. I want to travel all the way, like a dream.
I want to travel like this tomorrow
Let's seize the moment
Always.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
What? The second one?
Thanks for your help.
I made a mistake. Was it good? It was good. I made a mistake. And I've never danced or sung before. At first, I was lagging far behind.
Minami. And then....
Minami-san..,Minami said,
I'll do my best!" and sang "I'll do my best!
Minami sang, "I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'm going to be a great strength as I start to run
A little more tenderness is what I want, I felt like I was embarrassed
If it overflows, this battle will continue
for a long time.
Thank you very much.
We're all having a drink.
Good morning.
Minomi, you've grown up a lot since the camp.
She showed us that she has grown up a lot since the camp.
And the one who was more nervous than anyone else...
I'm eating and eating a little bit... one of my issues is that I can't show my ability in the performance because of my nervousness.
One of my issues is that I am so nervous that I am not able to perform to my full potential on the day of the show.
One of the challenges I face is that I am too nervous to perform to my full potential on the day of an event.
One of the challenges I face is that I am too nervous to perform to my full potential on the day of the competition.
One of the challenges I face is that I am too nervous to perform to my full potential on the day of the competition. One of the challenges for Mr. Hiroshima is that he is unable to fully demonstrate his abilities in the performance due to nervousness.
What will it be like? Counting the raindrops for tomorrow
I'm counting the raindrops
I'm waiting for you to give me great strength.
See, you, my power
I can hear the sound of your overflowing, warm face melting aflame.
I look at you both and just think
I'm just thinking about you
I felt that a little bit of kindness was being born...
If only that one word overflowed, this battle was over! Thank you, everyone.
Yes, thank you very much.
At the training camp, my voice trembled and I thought I was less nervous and made mistakes than before.
Each of the finalists has shown a great deal of growth since the camp, and all of them performed equally well, supported by so many people, even their kindness.
Sometimes I forget people, and sometimes I put them away.
me
meme
Even me can do it, I'm sure
When I was about to fall into your hands
You reached out to me
From that day on
I did for you
The two of us of words
We were just getting started
In your story, we began to feel together
I felt like we were both being kind to each other
If only that one word overflowed, you'd be in this place
Currency
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
me
I was so moved that I said, "I've been in tears for a long time.
New members will be decided.